<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HelpStack Blog</title>
    <description>My thoughts on building HelpStack
</description>
    <link>http://helpstack.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://helpstack.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2015 11:18:06 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2015 11:18:06 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to progress with HelpStack</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;You want to provide customer support within your app and you have found HelpStack. You have gone through the features and you like it because it is open source, provides a wide variety of customizations and is available for both, iOS and Android..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But you think, &lt;em&gt;“Do I really want to use this? How will I make use of this?”&lt;/em&gt; This post will guide you through the process of progressing with HelpStack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;problem-0---faq--customer-support&quot;&gt;Problem 0 - FAQ &amp;amp; Customer support:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You have an app in the store. But you don’t get many downloads because your customers can’t understand it easily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;solution&quot;&gt;Solution:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You find HelpStack and you’re considering it for FAQ and Customer support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;problem-1---cost-effectiveness&quot;&gt;Problem 1 - Cost-effectiveness:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are not very clear if you want to pay for a helpdesk subscription since you are unfamiliar with them. You would like to get things done without incurring much cost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;solution-1&quot;&gt;Solution:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With HelpStack, you can see  that you can use a static list of FAQ articles that become part of your app locally. You also choose the Email Gear for incoming issues. Every issue that a customer creates and responds to, will now be sent as an email to you. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And it won’t cost you anything! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;problem-2---managing-a-sizeable-audience&quot;&gt;Problem 2 - Managing a sizeable audience:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your app is becoming fairly popular since you’re listening to your customers and making quick changes. But you are not able to handle the large volume of incoming e-mails because of your increasing popularity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You want powerful tools to respond quickly to customer issues, prioritize feature requests and assign more hands to help you with your app. You also want to maintain FAQ articles remotely, gather analytics data and generate reports of the incoming requests, to better understand what your customers want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;solution-2&quot;&gt;Solution:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HelpStack can be integrated with quite a few helpdesk solutions. So, go ahead and choose a helpdesk solution that serves your needs and select the equivalent Gear with HelpStack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, if you decide to use HappyFox as your helpdesk solution, you should choose the HappyFox Gear and integrate HelpStack with it by providing your HappyFox account’s credentials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HappyFox provides you the ability to prioritize incoming tickets, assign them to your customer support representatives, maintain FAQ articles remotely in a Knowledge Base, gather Analytics data, generate reports and much more. For a tour of features provided by HappyFox, visit this link: &lt;a href=&quot;https:// www.happyfox.com/ticket-support-system/&quot;&gt;https:// www.happyfox.com/ticket-support-system/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;problem-3---customisation&quot;&gt;Problem 3 - Customisation:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are an active user of HelpStack now and you love it! But you want more features, tailored specifically for your app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;solution-3&quot;&gt;Solution:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Create a new issue on our GitHub projects explaining the features you want. If you are feeling awesome, you can also fork the project, make changes, implement features yourself and share them back to us as a pull request, so that everyone can benefit from it. What are you waiting for?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are excited to use HelpStack, don’t forget to visit our project pages and add your app in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/happyfoxinc/helpstack-android/wiki/App-Showcase&quot;&gt;App Showcase&lt;/a&gt; wiki section.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HelpStack iOS - &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/happyfoxinc/helpstack&quot;&gt;https://github.com/happyfoxinc/helpstack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HelpStack Android - &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/happyfoxinc/helpstack-android&quot;&gt;https://github.com/happyfoxinc/helpstack-android&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can also show your love by tweeting to &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/helpstacksdk&quot;&gt;@HelpStackSDK&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2015 16:11:28 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://helpstack.io/helpstack-android/2015/03/02/how-to-progress-with-helpstack.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://helpstack.io/helpstack-android/2015/03/02/how-to-progress-with-helpstack.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>helpstack-android</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
